{
    "id": "b3d155e0a8ba4996b9804ff29bc1dd81",
    "title": "Formation Of Questions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ".................................... she have a sister?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Do",
                "Has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "048e5e39f2864ddb9b11c9baf7b0b68a"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... you have meetings on Mondays?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Had",
                "Do",
                "Does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "10afb578f53b453f95ca1303e47e8044"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... Jack speak many languages?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Do",
                "Has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cdc2b3445c6146e6b99c20490c998ee7"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................................... she ever speak rudely?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a979436c6d09421e8b060d9c2512a329"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ your kids like to watch TV?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6481e40537f24da2a63bb4ace6041490"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ she like him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a5a931fad2024db383f800b0814f0809"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. you often have meetings on Thursdays?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Have",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eaaee669b6304f4fabcb0657515299c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... it rain here in winter?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4fb0911088274eaba12ae9c8cd74c6ae"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................................... he play the guitar well?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "74fa4da90dfd405489bdcd977d907b7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... you believe in his integrity?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "38a92d06eae5453fb35239750ce38695"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... the elephant have a trunk?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "18f697cded174fc8ad788adf843ab807"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ........................................ James deal in?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1225da22c7984411bf61039bd9bcf4d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where ........................................... she work?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4584137c49444ff09f9a664020ae46bf"
        }
    ]
}